theartofjoomla.com 2015-06-18

# Privacy & Disclosure Policy – Eddify.me

This is my personal website written and edited by me. For questions about this site, please contact me. All content provided is for informational purposes only. The writings and posts on this website are my own and don’t necessarily represent the positions, strategies, or opinions of my employer or its subsidiaries. I make no representations as to the accuracy or completeness of any information found here or by following any links. I will not be liable for any errors or omissions in this information nor for the availability of this information. I will not be liable for any losses, injuries, or damages from the display or use of this information.

## Privacy Policy

The privacy of my visitors is extremely important. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected and how it is used.

First and foremost, I will never share your email address or any other personal information to anyone without your direct consent. Period.

### Log Files

Like many other websites, this website uses log files to help learn about when, from where and how often traffic flows to this site. The information in the log files include:

  * Internet Protocol addresses (IP)
  * Types of browser
  * Internet Service Provider (ISP)
  * Date and time stamp
  * Referring and exit pages
  * Number of clicks

All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and web beacons

Like nearly all Websites, this website stores “convenience” cookies on your computer whenever you leave a comment. These cookies record the name, and email address that you enter when you submit a comment so that you wont have to re-type that information the next time you leave a comment.

Third-party advertisers may also place and read cookies on your browser and/or use web beacons to collect information. This website has no access or control over these cookies. You should review the respective privacy policies on any and all third-party ad servers for more information regarding their practices and how to opt-out.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your web browser options.

Instructions for doing so and for other cookie-related management can be found on the specific web browsers’ websites.

#### Google Adsense

Google Adsense, a third party affiliate marketing network, uses cookies to help make sure I get a commission when you buy a product after clicking on a link or ad banner that takes you to the site of one of their merchants. You can read [Google Adsense Privacy Policy](http://support.google.com/adsense/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=48182).

#### Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics tool I use to help understand how visitors engage with this website. It reports website trends using cookies and web beacons without identifying individual visitors. You can read [Google Analytics Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html).

## Disclosure Policy

I make money on this site through affiliate programs. If you click an affiliate link or ad banner and buy the product, you help support this site because I’ll get a percentage of that sale.

Currently I’m an affiliate for Google Adsense.

What this means for you:

  * I do not and will not recommend a product just because I’m an affiliate.
  * I became an affiliate to earn some revenue towards the costs of running and maintaining this site. Where I have direct control over which ads are served on this site I offer only products that are directly related to the topic of this site and products that a reader/subscriber would have a genuine interest in or need of.
  * I do not recommend products just for the sake making money.
  * I recommend products because I think they are valuable to my readers.
  * I do not let the compensation I receive influence the content, topics, posts, or opinions expressed on this blog.
  * I respect and value my readers too much to write anything other than my own genuine and objective opinions and advice.

Just like this site, my Disclosure Policy is a work in progress. As the revenue streams evolve, so will this page.

Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is reviewed and revised from time to time. You will want to revisit it regularly. 

**Last Updated:** November 14, 2014.
